正如你所看到的那样  接收器本身是很简单的
As you can see, the receiver itself is pretty
你在这里可以看到Extends BroadcastReceiver这个类并重写onReceive方法
simple. Extend the broadcast receiver class and override the
接收器是轻量级的组件  是为了接收广播
onreceive handle as you can see here. Receivers are
做出反应并在五秒钟之内完成
lightweight components meant to listen for broadcasts, reacts, and complete
这五秒钟意味着简单的启动一个服务或发送一个通知完成
within five seconds that usually means simply starting a
要使你的接收器开始接受广播
service or sending a notification. To have your receiver
你可以通过类似这样的列表式接收器
start listening for broadcasts, you need to register it
来注册信息或者是像这样的
either through an entry in your manifest like this or
动态的和其他应用程序的组件在通常情况下是互动的
dynamically within another application component usually an activity,
然后你定义Intent-Filter可以选择
like this. Then you define the intent filter that
你想接收的特定的广播信息
specifies the broadcast event you want to receive.
你可以完成接收特定的信息通过像这里的代码这样
You can do that either here in the manifest
或者你可以注册你的带有应用程序组件例如一个Activity的接收器
or if you're registering your receiver with an
你可以像这样创建你的新的Intent-Filter
application component such as an activity, you can create
对于列表式的接收器和动态的接收器
your new intent filter like this. The biggest difference
最大的区别就是当他们在触发的时候
between manifest and dynamic receivers is when they're triggered.
一个经过编程的接收器会仅仅在应用程序运行的时候
A programmatically-registered receiver will only receive broadcasts while
接收广播的消息  当一个列表声明了接收器
the app is running. While a manifest declared
将会开始运行您的应用并去接收
receiver will start your app specifically to receive
特定的您的广播  举个例子
your broadcasts. For example, I usually code with
我经常在带着我的降噪耳机的时候Coding
my noise cancelling headphones on, so a music
所以一个音乐类的应用程序可能需要注册一个
app like this might want to register a runtime
运行时接收的系统在耳机没有插入的时候
receiver to listen to the system intent broadcast
系统应该试图去广播耳机没有插入
that announces when headphones are unplugged. That will allow
这将使它能够自动的暂停播放  当你的音频路由从耳机到外放时
it to automatically pause playback, when your audio routing switches
在这种情况下  我们可以使用
from headphone to speakers. In this case, we can use
一个在运行时的接收器  因为应用程序保证了
a runtime receiver, because the app is guaranteed to be
音乐在正常播放的时候接收器在运行  另一方面
running if music is playing. On the other hand, if I'm
如果我使用Google云消息从我的服务器上监听到新的数据
using Google Cloud Messaging to listen for new data from
我想要去注册一个列表式的接收器会不断的从我的服务器
my server, I want to register a manifest receiver that always listens
监听不断的传入的数据  并且它将唤醒我的程序
for incoming tickles from my server and will wake up
如果应用程序被终止触发更新应用
my app if it's being terminated to trigger the update code,
通常是一个同步适配器  这是我们将在后面的第六课
usually a sync adapter, which is something we will discuss
要讨论的内容  有非常多的广播系统可以帮助你的应用程序
later in lesson six. There's a bunch of system broadcasts
在系统中做出变化并及时的反应
you can monitor to help your app react to changes
你可以看到系统广播的动作在developer.android.com
in the system. You can see the system broadcast actions within
上面的Intent文档部分广播接收器的一大用途是
the intent documentation at developer.android.com. One great use for broadcast
监测变化的互联网连接或者是否是在充电状态
receivers is to monitor for changes to internet connectivity or
想象一下你的应用程序需要上传一部电影
charging status. Imagine your app has to upload a movie
或计算象棋游戏中接下来的10,000步
or calculate the next 10,000 moves in a game of chess,
你如何使用一个接收器去等待设备
how might you use a receiver to wait until the device is plugged in
插入之前的启动过程  它应该是一个
before starting that process? Should it be
列表式接收器还者是广播接收器
a manifest receiver or a broadcast receiver?